http://www.cityblossoms.com/terms-and-conditions.php

(212) 346-0756
sales@cityblossoms.com
Login
Shopping Cart
HomeShopVirtual Design Class- Textured Holiday Arrangement KitHoliday CollectionHanukkah collection-NEW!Designer's ChoiceSignature CollectionRosesCity Hall WeddingsPlantsColorsBlueYellowOrangePinkPurpleRedWhiteWeddingCity Hall WeddingsPersonal FlowersCeremoniesReceptionsRentalsWedding InquiryEventSocial EventsCorporate EventsEvent Inquiry FormCorporateWeekly Corporate AccountsResidential accountsHolidaysLandscaping and GardeningCorporate Inquiry FormAboutBlogGalleriesHanukkah collection-NEW!ClassesPressRentals
Home > Terms and Conditions
Terms and Conditions
Privacy StatementThis privacy statement is our commitment to protecting customer privacy. We do not knowingly solicit data from minors, nor do we knowingly market to minors.  We require that minors under the age of 18 use this service in conjunction with their parent or guardian.Information We Collect:  If you open an account on our site, we need your contact information including your name, email address, contact phone number and mailing address.  We use your purchase history, contact information and other registration information to send you information and to otherwise enhance your shopping experience with City Blossoms. If you choose to opt out of our email list, please send an email to sales@cityblossoms.com and put “please opt-out” in the subject line.  When you visit our website, we also collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. We use this information to determine our users demographics and interests, so that we can better understand and serve our users.Our Use and Disclosure of Your Information:  We may send emails to our users announcing special promotions, changes in our services or other information we believe will be of interest to our users.  If you prefer not to receive email, you can send us an email with the subject line “no emails” or reply to our email with the subject line “no emails”.  If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities on our site, we may collect information.  We may use that information and other information that we obtain from your use of our site to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreement for Terms of Use.We do not share aggregate statistics about our sales, traffic patterns and related site information with other businesses. We do not share customer names and addresses with other vendors.The only exception is, we may be required to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.  We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that may be illegal or may expose us to legal liability.Security: This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All user credit card information is securely communicated using secure socket layer (SSL) software, which is the industry standard among the best software available for secure commerce transactions.Linked Sites: If this site contains any links to other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.Changes to Privacy Statement: We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time. You should check this page periodically for changes.  By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by us as described in the Privacy Statement.   Questions and Comments: We welcome your questions and comments about this Privacy Statement.Safe Shopping Policy: When you shop with your payment and personal information is conducted and communicated using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software.  Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions.  It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.
As Seen On:
© 2020 City Blossoms. All Rights Reserved.
